[
  {
    "section": "Reasoning",
    "sectionNumber": 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "prompt": "Rebecca is louder than Kate",
        "questionText": "Who is less loud?",
        "choices": [
          {
            "text": "Rebecca",
            "isCorrect": false
          },
          {
            "text": "Kate",
            "isCorrect": true
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Tracy has more money than Stephen",
        "questionText": "Who is poorer?",
        "choices": [
          {
            "text": "Tracy",
            "isCorrect": false
          },
          {
            "text": "Stephen",
            "isCorrect": true
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Stewart is stronger than Joe",
        "questionText": "Who is stronger?",
        "choices": [
          {
            "text": "Stewart",
            "isCorrect": true
          },
          {
            "text": "Joe",
            "isCorrect": false
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Joshua is not as flexible as Chris",
        "questionText": "Who is less adaptable?",
        "choices": [
          {
            "text": "Joshua",
            "isCorrect": true
          },
          {
            "text": "Chris",
            "isCorrect": false
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "prompt": "Emma is not as talented as Tiffany",
        "questionText": "Who is more unskilled?",
        "choices": [
          {
            "text": "Emma",
            "isCorrect": true
          },
          {
            "text": "Tiffany",
            "isCorrect": false
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "section": "Perceptual Speed",
    "sectionNumber": 2
  },
  {
    "section": "Number Speed and Accuracy",
    "sectionNumber": 3
  },
  {
    "section": "Word Meaning",
    "sectionNumber": 4
  },
  {
    "section": "Spatial Visualisation",
    "sectionNumber": 5
  }
]
